ILGWU Arbitration Proceedings and Joint Board Minutes 5780/182
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Minutes of the Board of Grievances, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  February 13
- Minutes of Meetings of Grievance Board, Wage Scale Board, Conferences, and Special Investigations, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Proceeding Between the Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association, and Local 25, Waist and Dressmakers' Union, Local 10, Cutters' Union, and the ILGWU, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  November 6-7
- Wage Scale Board, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Volume 2. July 8
- Wage Scale Board, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Volume 3, July 8
- Board of Arbitration Proceedings in the Dress and Waist Industry, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  May 17
- Grievance Board, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  January 13
- Grievance Board, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Adjourned Arbitration Proceedings, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Volume 5. February 14
- Arbitration Proceedings Between the Ladies' Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association and the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Volume 6. February 26
- Arbitration Proceedings Between the Dress and Waist Manufacturers and the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Volume 7. February
- Arbitration Proceedings Between the Ladies' Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association and the ILGWU, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Volume 4. February
- Arbitration Proceedings, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  March 31
- Hearing Before the Committee of Immediate Action in the Matter of the Union Complaint Charging a Lockout Against the Firm of Adler and Ast, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  April 19
- Arbitration Proceedings Between the Ladies' Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association and the ILGWU, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Volume 8. January 20
- Board of Arbitrators Meeting Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union, and the ILGWU, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Case against Nathan Schuss and Company, November 25, 1914
- Board of Arbitrators Meeting Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union and the ILGWU, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Case against Nathan Schuss and Company; Volume 2, December 28, 1914
- Board of Arbitrators Meeting Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Case against Nathan Schuss and Company; Volume 3, January 20, 1915
- Arbitration Proceedings of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions of New York, and the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  August 3-6
- Arbitration Proceedings of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions of New York and the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Volume 2; August 5
- Arbitration Proceedings of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions of New York and the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Volume 2; October 12-13
- Council of Conciliation to Conciliate Matters Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  July 15
- Council of Conciliation to Conciliate Matters Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  July 13
- Council of Conciliation to Conciliate Matters Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Volume 2; July 17
- Council of Conciliation to Conciliate Matters Between the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Executive Session Volume 2; July 20
- Proceedings of Arbitration Board on Working Conditions to be Established in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry of Chicago, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  September
- Report of Board of Arbitration between the Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, North West Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association and Local 18, 44 and 81 of the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  September 24, 1915 (2 copies)
- Adjourned Session of the Board of Arbitrators in the Cloak and Suit Industry, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  January 23 and 24
- Minutes of Meeting between members of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association and members of the Garment Makers' Union, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  December 11
- Adjourned meeting of the Board of Grievances of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association and the Joint Board of the cloak and Skirt Makers' Union, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  February 17
- Meeting of the Board of Grievances of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, the Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Meeting of the Board of Conference [Grievance] of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, the Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions and the ILGWU, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  March 16
- Executive Session Committee of Council of Conciliation for the purpose of taking the testimony of the representatives of various Local of the Unions, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  July 17
- Administrative Board, Dress Industry New York City, Report, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  December 31
- Mayor's Conference to Initiate Proceedings to Bring About a Settlement of Questions in Controversy between the Manufacturers' Association and the Unions in the Cloak and Suit Industry, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  July 10
- Conference between a Committee of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association and a Committee of the ILGWU, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  May 23 and 31
- Report on Wage Increase Decision Rendered by the Impartial Chairman, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Los Angeles Coat and Suit Industry